<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GasOrder</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">ICT GAS STORE</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">group3_SE@ictk60</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="gasCode_prompt">12 Kg Petrolimex Cylinder (325.000 VND)</string>

    <string-array name="gasCode">
        <item>12 Kg Petrolimex Cylinder (300.000 VND)</item>
        <item>NaMiLux Mini Cylinder (200.000 VND)</item>
        <item>45 Kg Petrolimex Cylinder (1050000 VND)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="tips_text_1">     Do a body safety check before turning on your gas stove. To prevent any fires while using your gas stove, roll up your shirt sleeves above the elbow and tie back long hair with a rubber band. If you have any jewelry on, remove it before starting the stove. Turn the stove dial on to light the stove. Most gas stoves are equipped with a dial that lights the burner. You can usually adjust the heat to low, medium, and high depending on what you\'re using the stove for. Twist the dial and wait for the burner to light, then adjust it to your desired heat setting. \n
        Light the gas stove manually as an alternative. If your gas stove igniter is broken, most gas stoves can be lit with a match or lighter. Turn the gas dial to medium, then ignite your match or lighter. Hold the match or lighter close to the center of the burner, then wait 3-5 seconds until the burner ignites. Remove your hand quickly to prevent getting burned. \n\n</string>

    <string name="tips_text_2">     1. Check your stove\'s pilot light if it is an older model. Most older gas stoves are equipped with pilot lights, which stay on constantly even if the stove is off. Check with your stove manufacturer to see if your stove has a pilot light. For models with a pilot light, remove the burner grates from your stove and open the cooktop panel. The pilot light should be a small flame located directly below the stove panels.\n
        2. Always keep your stove attended when it\'s on. When cooking with your gas stove, never leave the room. A fire can start within seconds if your food is left unattended, and it is important to keep your burners in sight at all times. \n
        3. Use your gas stove for cooking only. Gas stoves are made to be used only for cooking food. Never use your stove for heating your home, as keeping the stove lit for extended amounts of time increases the likelihood of a gas leak. \n
        4. Watch for a hissing sound or the smell of natural gas. If you smell a sulfurous, "rotten egg" odor or hear a hissing sound coming from your stove, exit your home immediately and call emergency services. Your stove may be leaking natural gas, which can be deadly if it is not fixed immediately. \n\n
        5. Stock your kitchen with a fire extinguisher in case of emergency. Keep a fire extinguisher in a cabinet near your gas stove in case of grease fires. Store baking soda in the same cabinet as well, as pouring baking soda on the flames can stop small grease fires. \n\n</string>

    <string name="tips_text_3">     1. Unplug the stove before cleaning it. While cleaning your stove, you may need to use water, dish soap, and other cleaners. To avoid electrocution, unplug your stove range before you begin working. If your stove was recently on, wait until the stovetop cools down before cleaning.\n
        2. Remove your stove\'s burner grates and clean them separately. Take your burner grates off of the stove and place them in the sink. Then, fill the sink with hot, soapy water. Let your burner grates soak for several minutes, then clean them off with a wet sponge or dishcloth.\n
        3. Brush any crumbs off of the stovetop with a dry cloth. After all of the crumbs are brushed away, spray your stovetop with a spray bottle filled with a 1:1 water-white vinegar ratio. Let the mixture sit for a few minutes, then wipe it off with a wet sponge or dishcloth. \n
        4. Put the grates and burner caps back on. After wiping off any crumbs and stains from the stovetop, dry off burner grates and caps. Place the grates and caps back in place to reassemble the stove and make it ready for use again. \n
        5. Clean the stove knobs and back panels, if needed. Wipe off the stove knobs and back panel with a wet washcloth to remove any dust or minor stains. If there are larger food stains on your knobs or panels, spray them with the vinegar-water mixture and let it sit for several minutes before wiping them off again.\n\n</string>

    <string name="tips_text_4">     The stove is the real workhorse of the kitchen, and even more so when you\'re cooped up because of a winter storm and, er, cooking up one. But do you really know how to use it safely?Here are 10 stove safety tips every cook should know, according to Doug Rogers and Anthony Arroyo of Mr. Appliance repair services. \n
        What\'s an anti-tip bracket, you might ask? It\'s the thing that comes with most ovens and is usually tossed aside without a second thought. But it has a purpose: It keeps the stove in place, which is particularly good if you have small kids around who might try to use the opened oven door as a step.\n
        You probably already know to turn pot handles so they\'re not hanging out over the stovetop edge, which keeps kids and errant elbows from knocking them. But here\'s another smart tip: Use the back burners first, so hot pots are further from the edge.\n
        Sometimes you want your pan to be really hot, and that\'s fine — if you keep an eye on it. "When a pan is on high heat with nothing or just oil in it, it will heat up very quickly, and can be a fire risk: The oil or grease or even the lining on the pan itself could ignite," Arroyo says. \n\n</string>

    <string name="tips_text_5">     Sometimes our cleaning tools need a good cleaning themselves. Kitchen sponges — the squishy soft ones made of cellulose fiber — are sneaky harbors of bacteria, mold and yeast. They provide a damp oasis for these invisible foes that, when left to thrive, can become a microscopic colony of hazards to your family\'s health. Before you swear off sponges for good, here are two ways the scientists at the United States Department of Agriculture recommend cleaning them.</string>

</resources>
